ADRIÁN PEDRAZA MALLORQUÍN





in /ADRIANPEDRAZAM

WHO I AM

Hi there,

My name is Adrián Pedraza. I'm a Fullstack Designer. This means that I have knowledge from every stage of the design process, from the earlier design steps to front-end design.

Within all these, UI design and HTML & CSS development are my main strenghts, since those are the tasks I have been doing for most on my working life.

Lately I have been introducing myself more and more into all the UX processes and I expect to keep going through this wonderful path of Product design and Costumer experience.

I consider design a way of storytelling and belive that stories are universal tools. That's why I stand for an open web accesible and understandable for everyone, no matter who, how or where.

After a year working and wandering Australia, I'm back in Madrid trying to find new challenges that help me grow on my professional career.

LANGUAGES



native



IELTS 7.5



medium (A2)

WHAT I DO

USER EXPERIENCE

Information Architecture ★ ★ ★ ★ ★ Interface Design ★ ★ ★ ★ ★ Wireframing ★ ★ ★ ★ ★ Branding ★ ★ ★ ★ ★

USER INTERFACE

Composition * * * * *

Prototyping * * * * *

Interaction * * * *

Responsive Web Design * * * *

Component Design * * * *

Graphic Design * * *

TOOLS

Adobe Photoshop * * * * *
Adobe Illustrator * * *
Sketch * * * *
Invision * * *
Pen and Papers * * *

I ALSO DO FRONTEND

HTML5 & CSS3 * * * * *

JavaScript * * * *

Bootstrap 3 * * * *

Scrum * * * *

PEOPLE WHO THINK I'M DOING IT WELL

EMILY HAWKES

(Product Manager Console Group)

email: ehawkes@console.com.au phone: 0061415915086

contact time: 17:00 - 01:00 (UTC+2)

JORDAN MAIOLO

(Project Manager AGS Spain)

email: jordan.maiolo@axa-groupsolutions.com

phone: 0034625335351

contact time: 09:00 - 17:00 (UTC+2)

KATERINA MELANITU

(Design Coordinator AGS Spain)

email: katerina.melanitu@axa-groupsolutions.com

phone: 0034651675512

contact time: 09:00 - 17:00 (UTC+2)

LLUIS SANCHEZ

(Project Manager AGS Spain)

email: lluis.sanchez@axa-groupsolutions.com

phone: 0034615299165

contact time: 09:00 - 17:00 (UTC+2)

THINGS I NEED FOR SURVIVING...



films & tv



hiking



reading



caffeine

EXPERIENCE

CONSOLE GROUP (MAY 2017 - DEC 2017)

UX/UI Designer.

- Web designer for a Real Estate software provider.
- Design and presentation of webpages' interfaces
- UX/UI enhancenments for their management platform.

SOPRA STERIA

(OCT 2014 - FEB 2017)

Frontend Development & UX/UI Design for web.

- Consultant in Group AGBAR and AXA Group Solutions
- UI Design & Implementation
- UX User testing
- HTML & CSS Expert

FREELANCE

(JAN 2014 - OCT 2014)

Freelance web design & Wordpress development.

- Branding and web design
- Custom theming for Wordpress
- End-to-end development

OPINNO

(APR 2013 - JAN 2014)

Web master & Design for Wordpress.

- Platform Innovators Under 35 prize of MIT Technology Review.
- Web Design and banners
- Webmaster of all Latam, Spain and France sites

MOBAIL APPS

(APR 2010 - FEB 2011)

Graphic Design Internship.

- Design of interfaces, infographics, posters and general graphic material

EDUCATION

SMASHING CONF.

(OCTOBER 27, 2016)

Scalable and Modular Architecture for CSS.

- Full day workshop with Johnathan Snook